<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize>
<text id="EternalFlower_weapon_name">Gift of Eternity</text>
<text id="EternalFlower_weapon_no">Eternal</text>
<text id="EternalFlower_weapon_desc">There are many, many things unknown, even in the midst of eternity...</text>
<text id="EternalFlower_weapon_sdesc">For every 15 points of damage dealt by this E.G.O. Weapon, the wielder gains a stack of 'Truth'. "Behold the truth within this eternity."
Each stack of 'Truth' increases the wielders maximum SP by 3 points, and every 10 stacks of 'Truth' increases the damage dealt by 25%. "Gain power from the truth."
When the holder possesses the Key to 'Truth', each damage dealt will restore the spiritual and health values of the level of 'Truth' they possess.
The maximum numbers of stacks that can be possessed is 40, increases by 40 more if Flower of Eternity is present in the facility.
If Flower of Eternity is present during a suppression, the wielder immediately teleports to the vicinity of the target, with a cooldown of 15 seconds.</text>

<text id="EternalFlower_armor_name">The Perfect Flower</text>
<text id="EternalFlower_armor_no">Flawless</text>
<text id="EternalFlower_armor_desc">The concept of 'perfection' is a hoax. There's no such thing as 'perfection' in this world...</text>
<text id="EternalFlower_armor_special">30% of all damage taken is returned to the attacker. "Don't touch me... stay away... don't you dare leave so much as a blemish on me!"
Damage dealt by the wearer is increased by 50% if they are wielding 'Gift of Eternity'. "Eternity is not without its flaws..."
For every stack of 'Truth' the wearer possesses, movement speed and maximum HP increases by 3 points, and the maximum number of stacks increases by 60. "Truth? Such a thing doesn't exist, you know..."</text>

<text id="EternalFlower_gift_name">Key to 'Truth'</text>
<text id="EternalFlower_gift_desc">Max SP +10, all attributes +1 for every 5 stacks of 'Truth' owned.
'Truth' stack maximum increases by 20.</text>
</localize>